Help on built-in function lun_occult_when_loc in module swisseph:

lun_occult_when_loc(...)
    Find next occultation of a planet or star by the moon for a given geographic position (UT).

    :Args: float tjdut, int or str body, seq geopos, int flags=FLG_SWIEPH, bool backwards=False

     - tjdut: input time, Julian day number, Universal Time
     - body: planet identifier (int) or star name (str)
     - geopos: a sequence with:
        - geographic longitude, in degrees (eastern positive)
        - geographic latitude, in degrees (northern positive)
        - geographic altitude above sea level, in meters
     - flags: ephemeris flag, eventually ECL_ONE_TRY, etc
     - backwards: boolean, set to True for search back in time

    :Return: int retflags, (tret), (attr)

     - retflags: returned bit flags:
        - 0 if no occultation or eclipse found
        - ECL_TOTAL or ECL_ANNULAR or ECL_PARTIAL,
        - ECL_VISIBLE, ECL_MAX_VISIBLE, ECL_1ST_VISIBLE, ECL_2ND_VISIBLE,
          ECL_3RD_VISIBLE, ECL_4TH_VISIBLE
     - tret: tuple of 10 float, of which:
        - 0: time of maximum occultation
        - 1: time of first contact
        - 2: time of second contact
        - 3: time of third contact
        - 4: time of fourth contact
     - attr: tuple of 20 float, of which:
        - 0: fraction of planet diameter covered by moon (magnitude)
        - 1: ratio of lunar diameter to planet one
        - 2: fraction of planet disc covered by moon (obscuration)
        - 3: diameter of core shadow in km
        - 4: azimuth of planet at tjd
        - 5: true altitude of planet above horizon at tjd
        - 6: apparent altitude of planet above horizon at tjd
        - 7: elongation of moon in degrees (separation angle)

    This function raises swisseph.Error in case of fatal error.

    If you want to have only one conjunction of the moon with the body tested, add the following flag: ECL_ONE_TRY. If this flag is not set, the function will search for an occultation until it finds one. For bodies with ecliptical latitudes > 5, the function may search successlessly until it reaches the end of the ephemeris.

